kejsa.com 2015-04-26

# Privacy Policy - Bakoos Media

## Bakoos Privacy Policy

Bakoos enables people anywhere in the world to share information with others – locally, nationally and internationally – via the means of posting FEEDS in a microblog format allowing up to 160 characters. People can share information about any kind of topic, whether of a personal, general or business nature. The service can also be used to list a property (for sale or for rent) and to promote or to sell products and services. Any registered user can submit feeds which are automatically posted on the site for others to view instantly. Such feeds can also include links to other websites (sources) as well as photos or a video.

This Privacy Policy describes how and when Bakoos collects, uses and shares your information. Bakoos receives your information through our website. When using any of our Services you consent to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. Irrespective of which country you reside in or supply information from, you authorise Bakoos to use your information in the United Kingdom and any other country where Bakoos operates.

Collection and Use of your Information

** Information collected at Registration: **

When you create a Bakoos user account, you provide some personal information such as your name, username, email address, password and country & city of residence. Some of this information, for example your username and your country & city of residence are publicly visible on our Services, including on your profile page and in search results.

** User Image: **

Your ‘user image’ which can either be selected from a limited number of available options provided by Bakoos or uploaded by yourself directly from your computer using one of your own images, is also publicly visible on our Services and on your profile page. Please make sure to select an image as your ‘user image’ that you are happy to share with others (especially if you decide to use one of your own personal pictures). When creating a new account, your account will be set to display a pre-selected ‘user image’ as default; the default image can be changed in the “Edit Profile” section of your User Admin panel.

**Additional Information:**

You may provide us with additional profile information which will automatically show on your profile page, such as a short bio (biography), your website URL, and suitable keywords.

We may use your contact details to send you (by email) information and updates about our Services from time to time (including information about newly implemented services). As such information and updates about our network might be of importance to you, it is not possible at the present time to unsubscribe from receiving such notifications from Bakoos. By creating a user account, you agree to receive messages and updates from Bakoos.

**Feeds, Following and other Information:**

As our Services provide you with tools to communicate with others around the world, most of the information you provide to us is information you would want us to make public. This does not only include messages, information and other content you post on our Services in the form of Feeds, but also the use of any other Services provided through our network, such as the Property and Market sections and the Bakoos Shop (as well as any future services). Using certain Services might require for you to make public address details or a contact telephone number, f. ex. when using the Property and Market sections or the Bakoos Shop. Anything you submit on our Services (using the relevant submission forms) will be visible to others, unless you delete the information.

You should therefore think carefully about what you are making public when sharing information or content like photos, videos, and links via the Services.

**Location Information:**

Your location (city & country of residence) is automatically shown on your profile page. This information is required for us to channel and display your Feeds in your ‘local city hub’. Please note that is is NOT advisable for you to publish your personal address details with your feeds or in your Bakoos profile under any circumstances.

**Links:**

Bakoos may keep track of how you interact with links across our Services, including our email notifications. We do this to help improve our Services and to be able to share aggregate click statistics such as how many times a particular link was clicked on.

**Cookies:**

Like many websites, we use cookies and similar technologies to collect additional website usage data and to improve our Services. A cookie is a small data file that is transferred to your computer's hard disk. Bakoos may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better understand how you interact with our Services, to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic routing on our Services, and to customize and improve our Services. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can instruct your browser, by changing its settings, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. However, some Services may not function properly if you disable cookies.

**Log Data:**

Our servers automatically record information ("Log Data") created by your use of our Services. Log Data may include information such as your IP address, browser type, operating system, the referring web page, pages visited, search terms, and cookie information. We receive Log Data when you interact with our Services, for example, when you visit our website, sign into our Services, interact with our email notifications, or visit a third-party website that includes a Bakoos button or link. We use Log Data to provide our Services and to measure, customize, and improve them. If not already done earlier, we will either delete Log Data or remove any common account identifiers, such as your username, full IP address, or email address, after 18 months.

**Third Parties:**

Bakoos uses a variety of third-party services to help provide our Services and to help us understand the use of our Services, such as Google Analytics. These third-party service providers may collect information sent by your browser as part of a web page request, such as cookies or your IP address. Third-party ad partners may share information with us, like a browser cookie ID or cryptographic hash of a common account identifier (such as an email address), to help us measure ad quality and tailor ads. For example, this allows us to display ads about things you may have already shown interest in. If you prefer, you can turn off tailored ads in your privacy settings so that your account is not matched to information shared by ad partners for tailoring ads.

Sharing and Disclosure of your Information

**Your Consent:**

We may share or disclose your information at your direction, such as when you authorise a third-party web client or application to access your Bakoos account.

**Service Providers:**

We engage service providers to perform functions and provide services to us in the United Kingdom and abroad. We may share your private personal information with such service providers subject to confidentiality obligations consistent with this Privacy Policy, and on the condition that the third parties use your private personal data only on our behalf and pursuant to our instructions.

**Law and Harm:**

Notwithstanding anything to the contrary in this Policy, we may preserve or disclose your information if we believe that it is reasonably necessary to comply with a law, regulation or legal request: to protect the safety of any person; to address fraud, security or technical issues; to protect the rights or property of Bakoos. However, nothing in this Privacy Policy is intended to limit any legal defences or objections that you may have to a third party’s, including a government’s, request to disclose your information.

**Business Transfers:**

In the event that Bakoos is involved in a bankruptcy, merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets, your information may be sold or transferred as part of that transaction. The promises in this Privacy Policy will apply to your information as transferred to the new entity.

**Non-Private or Non-Personal Information:**

We may share or disclose your non-private, aggregated or otherwise non-personal information such as your public user profile information, public feeds and other content submissions made by you on our Services, the people you follow or those who follow you, or the number of users who clicked on a particular link.

Modifying your Personal Information:

If you are a registered user of our Services, we provide you with tools and account settings to access or modify your personal information and any information associated with your account.

Deleting your Account:

You can request to have your Bakoos account removed from our site. If you wish to have your account permanently deleted, please send us an “Account Deletion Request” using the Contact Form on our website. In order for us to delete your account, you will need to provide the following details: Your full name; your username; your email address (associated with the account); your password; your country & city of residence. We will need these details in order to identify your account and to ensure that you are the “rightful owner” of the account. It might take up to 30 days for us to delete your account. Once your account has been deleted from our system, it will not be possible to restore your account.

Our Policy towards Children:

Our website and its Services are not directed to persons under the age of 13. If you become aware that your child has provided us with personal information without your consent, please contact us using the Contact Form on our website. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we will take the necessary steps to remove such information from our system and terminate the child's account.

Changes to this Policy:

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version of the policy will govern our use of your information and will always be available on our website at [Privacy Policy](http://www.bakoos.com/dashboards/privacy_policy). If we make a change to this policy which, in our sole discretion, is material, we will notify you via a Bakoos update or by email to the email address associated with your account. By continuing to access or use the Services after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to [Contact Us](http://www.bakoos.com/dashboards/contact_us/).

**Effective from 01 June 2014**

﻿
